[{"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110311pmt", "aSentId": 67, "question": "I mean, there must have been a point where you thought you were all going to die, wasn't there?", "qSentId": 66}, {"answer": "From where we are, we're starting to continue to see more and more damage, Piers, as we get closer and closer.", "docId": "110311pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "Kyung, what's the latest from where you are?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "It's really hard to imagine.", "docId": "110311pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "Do you have any sense from what you're seeing, from what you're hearing about any kind of death toll?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110311pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "Can you describe to me what is actually going on?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "Thank you very much, Mr. Morgan, for giving me this opportunity.", "docId": "110311pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "Could you please start by telling me what your understanding of the scale of this disaster is in terms of people who've been wounded, possibly killed?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "As what I said is the figure that we have identified up to now.", "docId": "110311pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "I mean are you fearing here -- that you may be seeing a toll much, much higher?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "Yes, we are talking about the Fukushima nuclear power plant, and there are two sites.", "docId": "110311pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "Can you tell me what the latest is in relation to those plants?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "I am sorry, I'm not in a position to speculate on that.", "docId": "110311pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "I mean, is it possible we could see a meltdown of one of these plants?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Well, it's not the answer you want to hear, but I would say that statistical analysis would have a hard time finding a pattern here.", "docId": "110311pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "Ken, can I start with you and just ask you what you think is going on from an expert point of view here?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "110311pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "Is this actually how it sounds?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Well, I think Ken has a good point that if you looked at the geological history of this area, there's been repeated tsunamis generated in the Sendai area.", "docId": "110311pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "What do you think is happening here?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "It's complete nonsense, but I don't like saying it's nonsense without defending why it is so.", "docId": "110311pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "Is this complete nonsense, or is there any kind of credence to that theory?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "Well, aftershocks do follow some general patterns and can be statistically analyzed.", "docId": "110311pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "Is this one of the inevitable repercussions of an earthquake that size?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "ERKUS: Well, there's several things.", "docId": "110311pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "What possible comfort can you offer them?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "I think people should be texting to the Red Cross.", "docId": "110311pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "Given we've experienced this before there, what do you think is the most sensible and immediate thing that should be done to help the people in Japan?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "They -- when you shut down a nuclear plant, you're continuing to produce heat.", "docId": "110311pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "Matthew, if I may start with you, what is your understanding of the latest situation at the Fukushima plant?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "At this point, a meltdown is not inevitable.", "docId": "110311pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "What is the hour-by-hour time scale that we could be looking at before there's some sort of inevitable meltdown?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "Well, actually there haven't been very many situations of this degree of seriousness.", "docId": "110311pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "How serious do you think this one is in Japan?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "There's the beginning of renaissance in nuclear construction all over Asia and, to some extent, in the United States.", "docId": "110311pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "And what does it mean for nuclear plants in America, for example, if a similar thing was to happen here?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "First of all, Piers, our hearts and prayers are with the people of Japan, and the -- the Japanese American community that lives here in Los Angeles, the largest in the United States.", "docId": "110311pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "And if so, are we prepared to deal with it?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not an expert on that, but I can tell you the following: I got in real-time on my Blackberry.", "docId": "110311pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "How fast can these tsunamis strike, can these quakes strike?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110311pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "Is that just crass stupidity, in your view?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "No, definitely not.", "docId": "110311pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "Have you in your lifetime seen anything quite like what we witnessed in Japan in the last 24 hours?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "Incredibly active zone, Piers.", "docId": "110311pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "What is the ring of fire and what does it mean now going forward?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "Piers, if I could forecast the weather for the rest of the year, I would do it right now, go home and call it a day.", "docId": "110311pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "Is it now completely unpredictable?", "qSentId": 518}]